https://sterlingphotography.com/privacy

Skip to content
Privacy PolicyStaff2018-11-18T11:05:28+00:00
This website  is protected by United States Copyright Law.
The compilation, layout, organization, the company name, all images appearing, content (text), graphics, logos, layout, design, button icons, etc. are the sole and exclusive property of photographer and site owner, J.R. Sterling. This website and all associated with the website may not be reproduced, copied, distributed, transmitted, displayed, published or broadcast in any form without the expressed written permission of site owner, J.R. Sterling. Any entities not honoring this will be prosecuted to the full extent of the law.
Visitor information submitted through this website will be kept confidential and not shared with any entities. We take reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information as you transmit it to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure. The use of this website does not constitute any photography agreement between the visitor and the photographer, J.R. Sterling. Please complete our “contact form” or call our office directly at (407) 894.1111 to schedule photography services. We will get back with you promptly regarding our availability.
Disclaimer
By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. No guarantee is stated or implied by any verbiage or link presented on this website.  The site may contain outside links or references to other Web sites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply.
Go to Top
